Retribution is coming
Brimstone is a thriller, western, drama film directed by Martin Koolhoven.
In the menacing inferno of the old North-American West, Liz is a genuine survivor
who is hunted by a vengeful preacher for a crime she didn’t commit.
The Reverend, played by Guy Pearce.
Liz, played by Dakota Fanning.
Anna, played by Carice van Houten.
Samuel, played by Kit Harington.
Sally, played by Vera Vitali.
Joanna, played by Emilia Jones.
Brimstone is a 2016 psychological Western film
written and directed by Martin Koolhoven.
The film stars Dakota Fanning, Guy Pearce, Emilia Jones,
Kit Harington, and Carice van Houten.
It is a Dutch-American as well as French, German,
Belgian and Swedish international production.
The film was selected to compete for the Golden Lion at the 73rd Venice
International Film Festival on 3 September 2016, where it caused controversy.
It premiered in the Netherlands on 12 January 2017, where it was very well received, as in the rest of Europe
and was released on 10 March in the United States, where it received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of suicide, prostitute, rape, gun, obsession.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.